module.exports.global = [{
	id: '2569',
	name: 'HoneyBooBoo',
	level: 0,
	sprite: 0,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['What a weird robot that was! I wonder what it was doing? My head is full of fluff, but perhaps you could figure it out. But if it\'s not a bother, could you answer something for me first?  ', 'I\'m still waiting for your answer!', 'A wise bear once said "You can\'t stay in your corner of the Forest waiting for others to come to you. You have to go to them sometimes.” Which I think means you should go talk to my friends in order to help restore color to our world.']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'Guiding Values',
		feedbackRight: 'That will give me a lot to think about.',
		feedbackWrong: '',
		question: 'Choose one of the ethics you just read about and explain why it is important to you.',
		questionType: 'open',
		requiredLength: 100,
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l0,70l80,0l0,-70l-80,0z',
			fill: 'lightGreen'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '4284',
	name: 'Hoots',
	level: 0,
	sprite: 1,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['Hoo hoot! Owls are known to be wise. Some even say they are sages who watch over adventurers. Which is why I chose to resemble one, hoot! I  have something that could help you!', 'A famous owl once said "you will encounter many hardships ahead... that is your fate. Don\'t feel discouraged, even during the toughest times!" So, would you like to try again?', 'I knew you would prevail! You just needed a little wisdom.You should find the others in order to seek out the other pieces of the tri...I mean...puzzle.']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'Upstream or Downstream?',
		feedbackRight: 'Exactly! Maybe think about which approach appeals the most to you, too?',
		feedbackWrong: 'Hoo...boy. That\'s not right.',
		question: 'Imagine that you\'ve volunteered to help out as a soup kitchen by organizing donations, performing outreach, and preparing food for people in need. Would this be an example of...?',
		questionType: 'multiple',
		possibleAnswers: ['A) upstream-oriented service', 'B) downstream-oriented service', 'C) noble futility', 'D) none of these'],
		answer: 'B) downstream-oriented service',
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l50,-50l50,50l-50,50l-50,-50z',
			fill: 'blue'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '4693',
	name: 'Squirls',
	level: 0,
	sprite: 2,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['HI HI HI! I got a thing for you! you might want to see it! But first a question! But take your time! Think it through! Don\'t rush! Answer well! Use your brain! ', 'I\'m still waiting for your answer!', 'YAY! Woohoo! Color! I have nothing left for you! Go go go! Find the others! I can also show you the other answers!']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'What\'s Important',
		feedbackRight: 'Very interesting!',
		feedbackWrong: 'You might want to think about that a little more and try again.',
		question: 'There are many different ways you might serve the community. The resource talked about understanding root causes vs. just helping out any way you can. Which of these approaches appeals to you more? What do you see yourself doing in the future that addresses one or the other -- or both?',
		questionType: 'open',
		requiredLength: 20,
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l0,-90l60,0l0,-50l-140,0l0,140l80,0z',
			fill: 'lightBlue'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '6265',
	name: 'Rabby',
	level: 0,
	sprite: 3,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['I found these shiny objects while digging in my garden. Maybe one can help you? But I like them, so I\'ll only give it up if you really need it. So first a challenge!', 'I\'m still waiting for your answer!', 'After seeing your hard work, I see that its better to help others rather than hoard things. I don\'t have any more shinies.']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'What You Will Achieve',
		feedbackRight: 'That will give me a lot to think about.',
		feedbackWrong: '',
		question: 'Based on what you\'ve seen, set one goal and one objective for yourself.',
		questionType: 'open',
		requiredLength: 100,
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l-50,50l50,50l0,-100z',
			fill: 'orange'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '8542',
	name: 'Foxy',
	level: 0,
	sprite: 4,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['Ah! Bonjour, my friend! Welcome to my French corner of ze forest! You\'re on a some sort of quest, no?  Perhaps you find the color, oui?  Help me and I will help you!', 'Oh no! Maybe you need another attempt. Try again, oui?', 'Q: How many seeds does it take to fully recolor our world? A: We\'ll never know unless you dare to find out!']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'Power and Privilege',
		feedbackRight: 'You are SO right.',
		feedbackWrong: 'Are you sure about that? Maybe take another look.',
		question: 'Based on the quote, do you think Dr. Norieta would agree with the following statement? "People who help others, but do so simply to feel good about themselves, or out of a sense of charity, are not approaching service from a productive angle."',
		questionType: 'yesno',
		answer: 'yes',
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0c0,0 60,0 60,0c0,0 0,-50 0,-50c0,0 -60,0 -60,0c0,0 0,50 0,50z',
			fill: 'orange'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '8956',
	name: 'Turp',
	level: 0,
	sprite: 5,
	isHolding: false,
	dialog: {
		smalltalk: ['Think about your strengths. Is there a way to leverage them further? Assess your challenges. Are there any opportunities to develop an area or skill you would like to improve?','My Great Grandturpy used to always say "Unless you try to do something beyond what you have already mastered, you will never grow." I\'m not sure if he meant that literaly or figuratively. It also sounds like something Emerson once said, but what do I know; I\'m just a turnip.', 'future']
	}
}, {
	id: '2176',
	name: 'RoggaBogga',
	level: 0,
	sprite: 6,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['Rogga has a thing that maybe help you grab and carry pretty colors back to world.  Sad with no color. Everything so gray. Maybe help with my survey and I give you thing?', 'I\'m still waiting for your answer!', 'Roga thinks you will be the best and bring back all the colors. Use all of the things! Want to see all of the things others say?']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'What Motivates You',
		feedbackRight: 'That will give me a lot to think about.',
		feedbackWrong: '',
		question: 'Which of these students resonated most with you? Why?',
		questionType: 'open',
		requiredLength: 50,
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l-100,0l0,50l60,0l0,20l80,0l0,-20l60,0l0,-50l-100,0z',
			fill: 'green'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '1608',
	name: 'Goku',
	level: 0,
	sprite: 7,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['O-o-oh... h-h-hi. I\'m h-holding something important for you.', 'This is tough, but important to think about!', 'I wish I was b-b-brave like you!']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'Struggles with Identiy',
		feedbackRight: 'Thanks for sharing that.',
		feedbackWrong: '',
		question: 'Describe a time you had difficulty communicating or collaborating with others because of some aspect of your social identities.',
		questionType: 'open',
		requiredLength: 150,
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l0,100l-50,-50l50,-50z',
			fill: 'lightOrange'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '4876',
	name: 'Quix',
	level: 0,
	sprite: 8,
	isHolding: true,
	dependsOn: [6265],
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['Oh! Hello! You startled me. I was just thinking about the answer to life, the universe, and everything. But you came to ask for help right? First, can you help me?', 'Hmm...It doesn\'t seem like you took my question seriously. This is important! You want to give me another answer?', 'Maybe the real answer to life, the universe, and everything can be found by working with people rather than with a super computer? If so, you should try talking to the others! Maybe you can help them and find the answer?']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'Thinking About Goals',
		feedbackRight: 'I can think of 42 reasons why that\'s a great answer.',
		feedbackWrong: '',
		question: 'Choose and answer one of these 12 questions in detail. How does it effect your goals and objectives?',
		questionType: 'open',
		requiredLength: 50,
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l0,-50l200,0l0,50l-200,0z',
			fill: 'green'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '6707',
	name: 'Bunzo',
	level: 0,
	sprite: 9,
	isHolding: false,
	dialog: {
		smalltalk: ['Is there potential for any aspect of your community work to connect to your academic coursework? Is there a political issue you are unsure about and would like to learn more?', 'I think helping others is so totally awesome. So I think you are so totally awesome for helping us. If I had hands, I would give you a high five!', 'future']
	}
}, {
	id: '9536',
	name: 'Malo',
	level: 0,
	sprite: 10,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['CHEWY CHOMP! I hear you\'re trying to spread some color. That\'s great. But first, chew on this!', 'I\'m not bad, I\'m just rendered that way. Give it another shot, why don\'t ya?', 'GOT ANY GUM? No? Oh well. I can show you the resource again, if you want.']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'Social Identities At Work',
		feedbackRight: 'Nailed it! We should totally hang out after this.',
		feedbackWrong: 'Hmm... never heard that one before. Maybe you should check out the resource one more time and give it another shot.',
		question: 'List three or more aspects of social identity that the students referenced in the video you just viewed.',
		questionType: 'open',
		requiredLength: 15,
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l80,0l0,90l-80,0l0,-90z',
			fill: 'lightGreen'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '8986',
	name: 'Jawa',
	level: 0,
	sprite: 11,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['This haircut is new. Tell me I look good, and I\'ll give you the chance to get some really cool stuff. Oh, you flatterer, you. Here\'s something that might help you...', 'This time, for sure. Presto!', 'I\'m tired of this haircut. Or maybe I\'m just bored with life. Either way, something\'s gotta change! You need to get out there and take life by the horns.']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'How Your Experiences Shape You',
		feedbackRight: 'Very revealing, but of course there\'s more to you than that.',
		feedbackWrong: 'Are you sure you understood the question? Try again!',
		question: 'List what you believe are five of the most important aspects of your identity, that intersect to make up who you are.',
		questionType: 'open',
		requiredLength: 40,
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l0,100l50,-50l-50,-50z',
			fill: 'lightOrange'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '8427',
	name: 'Fork',
	level: 0,
	sprite: 12,
	isHolding: false,
	dialog: {
		smalltalk: ['Would you like to volunteer in the community as a means of deciding if a certain career is right for you? 6.Are you hoping to find your passion?','It\'s so sad the color was taken away, but I can’t shake the feeling that this has all happened before. It\'s almost like something is stealing it...?','future']
	}
}, {
	id: '1547',
	name: 'Awaa',
	level: 1,
	sprite: 13,
	isHolding: false,
	dialog: {
		smalltalk: ['Did you learn something you didn\'t already know from someone in our community? Everyone has unique knowledge to offer! Maybe not Roga...but most!', 'Have you seen any rainbows? I wish we still had rainbows. I remember when the rainbows went away before. I miss them.', 'I think you would be better off talking to someone from the Forest first.']
	}
}, {
	id: '1517',
	name: 'Hampton',
	level: 1,
	sprite: 14,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['Sup. You seen my bro, Framp? Hamp loves Framp. We OWN this part of town! This is our turf! If you are gonna help our community you gotta let us help too!  Let me drop some knowledge on you.', 'Yo you gotta get this right before I will do anything for you.', 'Yeah I guess you aren\'t so bad after all. My bro Framp said you were alright. I\'m glad we got someone who wants to work with us to fix our town.']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'Working With Chinatown',
		feedbackRight: 'Interesting. Very interesting!',
		feedbackWrong: '',
		question: 'Think about your preconceptions of Chinatown as a neighborhood. How do they differ from what you saw in the resource videos?',
		questionType: 'open',
		requiredLength: 100,
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l0,-80l-170,0l-10,0l0,200l120,0l0,-120l60,0z',
			fill: 'orange'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '352',
	name: 'Frampton',
	level: 1,
	sprite: 15,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['YO! Framp is stoked you came to visit! You meet my bro Hamp yet? He is a little intense, but he just wants to make sure we are partners working together to help our community.','2','See? I told you Hamp isn\'t such a bad dude! He just loves his town and wants to be a part of helping restore the color. We all want to help make our home a better place.']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'Digital Chinatown',
		feedbackRight: 'That\'s great! Thanks for sharing!',
		feedbackWrong: '',
		question: 'What did you learn from the video you selected?',
		questionType: 'open',
		requiredLength: 50,
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0c0,0 0,-200 0,-200c0,0 -120,0 -120,0c0,0 0,200 0,200c0,0 120,0 120,0z',
			fill: 'lightOrange'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '3335',
	name: 'Nosezo',
	level: 1,
	sprite: 16,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['You know the worst thing about having a giant nose? The jokes people tell you. I got this one recently: "He who put face in fruit drink get punch in the nose." Anyway, enough about me. You need help finding the color right? I can help!', 'Ah. I think you need to try again.', 'I think my nose is beautiful. Thanks for not making any dumb jokes about it!']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'All About Somerville',
		feedbackRight: 'Great work!',
		feedbackWrong: 'Maybe you should review the resource and try again...',
		question: 'True or False: Somerville has a very large number of non-profit organizations.',
		questionType: 'truefalse',
		answer: 'true',
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l100,-40l100,0l100,40l-300,0z',
			fill: 'green'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '4338',
	name: 'Siri',
	level: 1,
	sprite: 17,
	isHolding: false,
	dialog: {
		smalltalk: ['Remember, our community has so many assets  that will be beneficial to making it a better place. We might need help, but let us be involved!', 'People keep confusing me with another Siri. Apparently she is pretty and is super smart! Maybe she is related to that other weird robot that is wrecking everything?', 'I think your keyboard will help you move around. Remember, Walk forward, Step backward, Angle left, and Dodge right. WASD!']
	}
}, {
	id: '6177',
	name: 'Chiklet',
	level: 1,
	sprite: 18,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['Listen. I\'m taking precious time out of my scientific research to talk to you. If you need some material from me, the least you can do is help me with my research.', 'Theres no way I\'m helping you without you helping me first.', 'Thanks for the help. Maybe there is some hope in the human race after all.']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'All About Medford',
		feedbackRight: 'That\'s right!  Mayor Michael McGlynn has overseen the rebuilding of every Medford elementary and middle school since he became the Mayor in 1988.',
		feedbackWrong: 'Maybe you should review the resource and try again...',
		question: 'True or False: The elementary schools in Medford are mostly outdated.',
		questionType: 'truefalse',
		answer: 'false',
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l100,0l0,-40l-50,-40l-50,40l0,40z',
			fill: 'lightGreen'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '7082',
	name: 'Hummer',
	level: 1,
	sprite: 19,
	isHolding: false,
	dialog: {
		smalltalk: ['Heyo! I just came across this killer quote: “Never doubt that a small group of thoughtful, committed people can change the world. Indeed, it is the only thing that ever has.” Just thought it would help inspire you to keep at it!', 'Aunty Hums used to tell me stories about the great color thief. How it stole all of the life from our community.Then a hero helped rally the community together to get it back. A real hero is someone who inspires others. Thats what my Hums used to say at least!', 'Did you help everyone in the forest already? I know they got hit pretty hard by the grayness.']
	}
}, {
	id: '7052',
	name: 'Dewdrop',
	level: 1,
	sprite: 20,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['Hullo. My name is Dewdrop. I have a cold *sniff*. I found this thing. It probably has germs on it, but I\'ll give it to you if you think it will help. You need to answer something for me first though.','I don\'t know why you would want this germ infested thing, but I can\'t give it to you until you answer my question.','Remember to always wash your hands, its the best way to prevent getting a cold! I don\'t have hands that I can wash, so thats probably why I\'m always sick.']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'What Host Communities Give Back',
		feedbackRight: 'Exactly right!',
		feedbackWrong: 'Oh, I don\'t think so. Maybe you should take another look?',
		question: 'True or False: Tufts Students use municipal services in our host communities, but Tufts plays no taxes to the communities.',
		questionType: 'truefalse',
		answer: 'true',
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l-60,0l0,120l-40,0l0,-160l140,0l0,160l-40,0l0,-120z',
			fill: 'green'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '9069',
	name: 'Zeebo',
	level: 1,
	sprite: 21,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['Hello there! Have you ever thought about how the alphabet would sound if it was one big word? Something like "ab-keddef-gajihkel-monop-quristuv-wixyz." My head hurts just saying that! Anyway, I found this weird looking thing. I will give it to you, but first I have make sure you will use it properly.', 'You\'re silly. Maybe you should say that alphabet-word outloud. Or at least answer that question for me.', 'You are the best! Make good use of that shape.']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'Working With Somerville',
		feedbackRight: 'I think that\'s probably true.',
		feedbackWrong: '',
		question: 'Based on what students, instructors, and stakeholders in Somerville said in the videos, what do you think makes Somerville unique in how it should be approached?',
		questionType: 'open',
		requiredLength: 100,
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l150,0l0,-120l-50,40l0,30l0,10l-100,40z',
			fill: 'blue'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '6773',
	name: 'BeepBoop',
	level: 1,
	sprite: 22,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['We need our color back. This is a community based need. You helping us solve a problem that we need help with is important to us, but its also important to learn about our community so you understand us! Heres a question for you.', 'Still waiting for that answer bub!', 'I\'m glad you are taking the time to learn about our world! By working with us and learning about our history your help will be so much more appreciated!']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'All About Chinatown',
		feedbackRight: 'Bingo! Now that\'s what I\'m talkin\' about!',
		feedbackWrong: 'That\'s not right! Check the resource and give it another shot.',
		question: 'True or False: The overwhelming majority of youth in Chinatown who speak an Asian dialect also speak English.',
		questionType: 'truefalse',
		answer: 'true',
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0c0,0 0,110 0,110c0,0 0,10 0,10c0,0 150,0 150,0c0,0 -100,-40 -100,-40c0,0 0,-40 0,-40c0,0 -50,-40 -50,-40z',
			fill: 'lightBlue'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '8898',
	name: 'Beholder',
	level: 1,
	sprite: 23,
	isHolding: false,
	dialog: {
		smalltalk: ['Like the magician\'s circle always says, "THE SHOW MUST GO ON!" You must go on and talk to the others.', 'Wanna see a magic trick? BEHOLD! I WILL PULL A RABBIT OUT OF MY FACE...err..that doesn\'t sound right...', 'How will I ever put on my magicshow if no one will be able to see all the pretty colors?']
	}
}, {
	id: '9170',
	name: 'Blooper',
	level: 1,
	sprite: 24,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['Bloop dee doop bloop! Beep boop? Oh. Sorry. You don\'t speak bloopian. What I said was: Are you here to help us? If so, I think we can help you help us!', 'This bloopin thing won\'t answer itself! ', 'If you haven\'t already talked to Zeebo, I bet he has some junk you could use to fix this mess!']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'An Assets-Based Approach',
		feedbackRight: 'Yes. Our philosophical approach for civic engagement work with community partners is from the asset-based model. This explains why all community-based projects and opportunities should be based on community-identified needs. This does not mean that you cannot be creative and have ideas for addressing challenging issues, but unless the idea is based on a community-identified need and agreed upon with a community partner, there is little chance of success.',
		feedbackWrong: 'That\'s not what we think. Try again, please!',
		question: 'In an assets-based philosophy, who should identify the challenges (needs) that should be addressed in the community?',
		questionType: 'multiple',
		possibleAnswers: ['A) Volunteers from outside should identify them, because they have a better perspective', 'B) Needs should be identified by assets within the community', 'C) Everyone should assess needs and act upon them without deliberation', 'D) Use a "take-it-as-it-comes" philosophy'],
		answer: 'B) Needs should be identified by assets within the community',
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l300,0l-100,-40l-100,0l-100,40z',
			fill: 'lightOrange'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '2649',
	name: 'Dunks',
	level: 1,
	sprite: 13,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['The best part about basketball is when you breakaway, rush the basket, and slam it through the hoop! Teamwork and collaboration is cool too I guess. I wish we had more basketball courts around here. But I guess getting color back is a priority. On my way home yesterday I found this. Maybe it can help?', 'Maybe you could try again. I take this stuff seriously you know! I won\'t just give this thing to anyone.', 'Hope that thing helps. Remember: basketball courts. Get on that.']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'Give And Take',
		feedbackRight: 'Insightful response, thanks!',
		feedbackWrong: '',
		question: 'Is there a time that you learned something from a community member, whether a child or an elderly resident, an organization leader or member, where you were “providing service’? Please describe below.',
		questionType: 'open',
		requiredLength: 30,
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0c0,0 0,-200 0,-200c0,0 150,0 150,0c0,0 0,40 0,40c0,0 -70,0 -70,0c0,0 0,160 0,160c0,0 -80,0 -80,0z',
			fill: 'lightGreen'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '3075',
	name: 'Isosceles',
	level: 1,
	sprite: 25,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['You humans crack me up. You all look the same! Calliope is filled with diversity. Zork and Framptonare so different, but they care about their home equally. Do you care about our community? Here is a question for you!', 'You have to do better than that!', 'Thanks for working with us. We gotta catch that darn robot! Without you it would be hard to organize all of these resources.']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'Digital Medford',
		feedbackRight: 'Neat!',
		feedbackWrong: '',
		question: 'What is one thing you learned from the website?',
		questionType: 'open',
		requiredLength: 50,
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l0,-200l150,0l0,40l-70,0l0,160l-80,0z',
			fill: 'orange'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '5063',
	name: 'Zork',
	level: 1,
	sprite: 25,
	isHolding: false,
	dialog: {
		smalltalk: ['This big open field is boring without all the colors. I guess I should be thankful I still have my mailbox and big house!','"I love caves. I heard someone once say "It is by going down into the abyss that we recover the treasures of life. Where you stumble, there lies your treasure." Maybe this means treasure is always found in caves? Or maybe it just means to try new things outside of your comfort zone.', 'Did you know you can give out seeds to other players? Click "Seed It!" if you like their public answers.  Make your answers public and others can give you seeds, too.']
	}
}, {
	id: '2803',
	name: 'Krampy',
	level: 1,
	sprite: 42,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['You\'re the one organizing the resources right? I seen types like you before. Coming in and trying to help our community without knowing anything about us. Maybe if you prove you aren\'t just here for glory and fame, and that you do want to help make Calliope a colorful world again, I will give you something that can help.', 'Try again, kid. ', 'My intial judgements about you might have been wrong. Still, I am keeping my eye on you! Don\'t try anything funny!']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'Who You\'ll Work With',
		feedbackRight: 'Yup, that\'s right!',
		feedbackWrong: 'Confused? Check out the resource one more time and try again.',
		question: 'You will choose to work in one of the three host communities closest to Tufts main campus. What are the three communities?',
		questionType: 'multiple',
		possibleAnswers: ['A) Somerville, Chinatown, and Medford', 'B) Somerville, Chinatown, and Worcester', 'C) Somerville, Worcester, and Medford', 'D) Grafton, Worcester, and Medford'],
		answer: 'A) Somerville, Chinatown, and Medford',
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l0,-200l-150,0l0,40l70,0l0,160l80,0z',
			fill: 'blue'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '3229',
	name: 'Goose',
	level: 1,
	sprite: 10,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['I heard that this far off place called Medford  is one of the oldest Afro-American communities in the United States.Thats pretty far out man! Could you tell me more about this world?','Aw cmon man! I want to know!','Thats groovy, man. I DIG. The gnarliest thing is learning about cool places! Makes you feel, you know, all like connected.']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'Working With Medford',
		feedbackRight: 'That\'s an idea!',
		feedbackWrong: '',
		question: 'Select one of the challenges facing Medford discussed in the videos, and talk about one of the ways you might work to overcome it.',
		questionType: 'open',
		requiredLength: 100,
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l0,-200l-150,0l0,40l70,0l0,160l80,0z',
			fill: 'lightOrange'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '3373',
	name: 'Starbuck',
	level: 1,
	sprite: 34,
	isHolding: false,
	dialog: {
		smalltalk: ['I always think its neat when new residents come to live in Calliope. Because we are from all over the universe, Calliope has so many different langauges and cultures. Diversity keeps things interesting.','I really hope this gray shroud goes away soon. The town just isn\'t the same without all the vibrant color flowing from the storefronts. Hope the resource collecting is going well.','You don\'t need to make your answers public, but if you do, other players can give you extra seeds.']
	}
}, {
	id: '4655',
	name: 'Apollo',
	level: 1,
	sprite: 4,
	isHolding: false,
	dialog: {
		smalltalk: ['Remember to talk to everyone you see. You never know who will have some useful asset that could help!','I think a real hero is someone who helps people help themselves. As much as I like videogames, I wish the heroes in them weren\'t so full of themselves!','You can give seeds to other players by clicking their public responses after you answer a question. But you only have five seeds to give out each level, so use them wisely.']
	}
}, {
	id: '5219',
	name: 'Toaster',
	level: 1,
	sprite: 10,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['FACT: French Toast, while delicious, is not true toast because it’s the eggy coating that is browned, not the bread itself.  Moreover it is typically prepared in a pan and therefore fried, not toasted. It should be called French Fried Egg. If you answer my question right I will give you another fact about toast. I guess I could also give you this other thing, but it isn\'t as interesting.', 'False. Try again.', 'Sorry my question wasn\'t about toast. I know how disappointing that must have been.']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'A Change of Perspective',
		feedbackRight: 'Hm, interesting. Thanks for sharing!',
		feedbackWrong: '',
		question: 'What do you think was gained by the youths that made this video? Do you think it was successful?',
		questionType: 'open',
		requiredLength: 50,
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l100,0c0,0 0,-40 0,-40c0,0 -50,-40 -50,-40c0,0 -50,40 -50,40c0,0 0,40 0,40z',
			fill: 'orange'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '5206',
	name: 'Blobby',
	level: 1,
	sprite: 46,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['I heard in this wacky place called..Somerville?...its always summer! Is that true? No? What a misleading name. What\'s unique about this place then if you can\'t just swim all the time!?', 'That doesn\'t make much sense.', 'In Calliope, there is no real weather, we just tell time by asking someone what time it is. That way, whatever time you want it to be is what time it is. Its complicated.']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'Digital Somerville',
		feedbackRight: 'Thanks for sharing that!',
		feedbackWrong: '',
		question: 'What is one thing you learned from the website?',
		questionType: 'open',
		requiredLength: 50,
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l0,-160l-140,0l0,160l40,0l0,-120l60,0l0,120l40,0z',
			fill: 'blue'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '17599',
	name: 'FryGuy',
	level: 2,
	sprite: 25,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['Welcome to our Ranch! Its pretty cool right? Like, a cool ranch? That reminds me of my favorite snack...wait, what were we doing again? Oh yeah! Bustin that color suckin robot! You might need this thing I think.','Get your head out of the dirt and get on this!','Glad I could help. Make sure you talk to everyone else around the ranch. If you find some Doritos, hit me up.']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'Power and Privilege: Race',
		feedbackRight: 'You got your helping hat on. I dig it.',
		feedbackWrong: '',
		question: 'In your own words, what is meant by "institutionalized racism" and "envirnoment racisim?"',
		questionType: 'open',
		requiredLength: 100,
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0c0,0 0,-30 0,-30c0,0 70,0 70,0c0,0 0,30 0,30c0,0 -20,0 -20,0c0,0 0,-10 0,-10c0,0 -30,0 -30,0c0,0 0,10 0,10c0,0 -20,0 -20,0z',
			fill: 'orange'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '16297',
	name: 'ChickenBob',
	level: 2,
	sprite: 26,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['Howdy youngin. My name is ChickenBob, the chickenest bob in all of Calliope. I got this there thangy that might help stop that darn robot from doin all that suckin.  Help me with somethin and I\'ll give it to ya.','Who do you think I am, youngin? You gotta put two turnips into the farm before you harvest the crops, you know? Try again.','Hey Allright! You take care now, ya hear? You see that machine,  you call up chickenBob and he\'ll sock it right in the nose!']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'Bridging The Gap',
		feedbackRight: 'I believe I can fly. I believe if you try you can fill the sky with color.',
		feedbackWrong: '',
		question: 'Out of all the advice given in the video, what did you find most helpful, and why?',
		questionType: 'open',
		requiredLength: 40,
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l-20,20l-20,40l0,110l100,0l0,-70l-60,0l0,-100z',
			fill: 'lightOrange'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '18552',
	name: 'Scallop',
	level: 2,
	sprite: 27,
	isHolding: false,
	dialog: {
		smalltalk: ['Did you know there are wacky secrets hidden around town? You need to talk to us to find them!','One day I washed up on the shore and ChickenBob gave me a home on the ranch. There are some great folks living in this place! It\'s good to get to know them. I think thats good advice for all places!','A wise Lorax once said: "Unless someone like you cares a whole awful lot,Nothing is going to get better. It\'s not."']
	}
}, {
	id: '14588',
	name: 'PenPen',
	level: 2,
	sprite: 28,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['Hey! Hey! You! That weird robot stole all the color! Whats the point of this awesome flag if the color is empty? Argh! Robots! Is this hinge going to help you?', 'ah you gotta show me that this thing will help so I can use my flag!', 'Did you know that flags are so fun? You can wave them, you can show your support for something, and you can wave them! So fun!']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'Reciprocity-Merging Your Objectives',
		feedbackRight: 'By George, I think you\'ve got it!',
		feedbackWrong: 'Perhaps you should re-read the resource and try again!',
		question: 'Which of the following are important aspects of making sure your efforts benefit both yourself and the community?',
		questionType: 'multiple',
		possibleAnswers: ['A) Maintaining a balance between your own learning and the service that you\'re providing', 'B) Respecting community members as co-educators and partners', 'C) Learning about the community’s assets as well as its needs', 'D) Truly addressing a need that the community itself identifies', 'E) All of These', 'F) A and B'],
		answer: 'E) All of These',
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l0,-60l300,0l10,20l0,40l-310,0z',
			fill: 'green'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '14464',
	name: 'Combover',
	level: 2,
	sprite: 29,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['My friend! Do come yonder and fill my space with all of your colors. Color, my friend, is one of the most precious gifts bestowed upon our community. A challenge for you then! The reward will prove your worth as a true adventurer!', 'You still must prove to me your worth, friend!', 'I used to be an adventurer like you, until my world got sapped of all its color. Go forth and restore!']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'Shared Goals and Objecitves',
		feedbackRight: 'Thanks for that! Keep fighting the good fight.',
		feedbackWrong: '',
		question: 'Do you know of a goal or objective that you and the organization both share? If so, what?',
		questionType: 'open',
		requiredLength: 2,
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l0,70c0,0 100,0 100,0c0,0 0,-70 0,-70c0,0 -100,0 -100,0z',
			fill: 'lightGreen'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '15472',
	name: 'Funguy',
	level: 2,
	sprite: 30,
	isHolding: false,
	dialog: {
		smalltalk: ['Did you know you can walk by using the W,A,S,D keys, or by clicking?','Its great that you came to Calliope to help us. Its a great responsibility. You know, like Spiderman! Great power is responsibility and its important. Something like that.','It would be better for you to visit the Forest or maybe the Town first.']
	}
}, {
	id: '12760',
	name: 'Rapscallion',
	level: 2,
	sprite: 31,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['My name always gets me in trouble. People kept blaming me for the lack of color! Like, just because my name means "rascal" doesn\'t mean I\'m a bad guy! You don\'t think I\'m a bad guy do you? Here! I got something that will help you! That will show em!', 'Well...I think you could do better. I just don\'t want to give up this piece if it isn\'t going to someone who will help us.', 'See! I told you I was a good guy! That should go to show that judging someone based on a first impression isn\'t a good idea!']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'Responsibility and Commitment',
		feedbackRight: 'That sounds like a great start. Now keep your commitment to us and bring back all the color!',
		feedbackWrong: '',
		question: 'Name a couple things you will do that will help ensure you meet your commitments to the community.',
		questionType: 'open',
		requiredLength: 40,
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l0,-70l150,0l0,70l-150,0z',
			fill: 'lightBlue'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '11752',
	name: 'Oriole',
	level: 2,
	sprite: 32,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['Oh, don\'t you just love Calliope? I swear to you its much more beautiful with the colors. That evil, evil, robot! Maybe I can help you put a stop to this gray madness? Then again, I wouldn\'t want to put you in any danger. Can I trust that you know how to be safe?', 'I\'m still waiting for that answer!', 'You don\'t need to make your answers public, but if you do, other players can give you extra seeds.']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'Safety First',
		feedbackRight: 'Glad to hear it!',
		feedbackWrong: 'This is important! Please go back and take another look.',
		question: 'Do you understand the safety policy of Tufts? If you will be working with people under the age of 17, have you taken the proper precautions and measures?',
		questionType: 'yesno',
		answer: 'yes',
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l20,0l0,-10l30,0l0,10l20,0l0,-30l-70,0l0,30z',
			fill: 'blue'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '14706',
	name: 'Toad',
	level: 2,
	sprite: 33,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['Before I came to Calliope, I used to live in this place with other mushrooms. It was cool, until this huge spiky turtle dragon thing started wrecking everything! That\'s when I found this place. I loved it here, that is until a dumb robot stole all the color. Can\'t a mushshroom get a break? I\'m sick of moving, so I\'ll help you stop this thing if you do something for me first.', 'Be a star. Answer the question!', 'Sorry, but your other resources are probably in another castle...er...area.']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'Power and Privilege: Poverty',
		feedbackRight: 'That\'s true. The poverty threshold for a single individual under the age of 65 is $11,334. Seems low, huh?',
		feedbackWrong: 'Nope! Try again, please.',
		question: 'True or False: A single individual earning $13,000 per year is not officially counted as poor.',
		questionType: 'truefalse',
		answer: 'true',
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l0,60l260,0l-20,-40l-20,-20l-220,0z',
			fill: 'lightOrange'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '16547',
	name: 'Threepee',
	level: 2,
	sprite: 34,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['Lucky for you, I can speak over six million langauges. If you want to communicate in Gleeboz or Krillin, just let me know and I can switch. In the mean time, maybe you can help show me how to be a professional. I will give you something neat if you do!', 'I\'m not so sure, but that seems a bit strange.', 'According to my calculations, the color has vanished many times before! I also learned that there is something called a mega seed. Sounds fascinating!']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'Keeping Professional Relationships',
		feedbackRight: 'Thanks for your answer!',
		feedbackWrong: '',
		question: 'Think of a time when you were expected to behave professionally. What did you feel was expected of you? How did you act to ensure a strong professional relationship?',
		questionType: 'open',
		requiredLength: 50,
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l0,40l300,0l-10,-20l-20,-20l-270,0z',
			fill: 'blue'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '10891',
	name: 'Beanie',
	level: 2,
	sprite: 35,
	isHolding: false,
	dialog: {
		smalltalk: ['Don\'t forget the true defintion of humility: the state or quality of being humble. Its important!','Remember! Personal goals benefit you and project goals benefit the community! When these two perspectives are both understood and combined, a foundation is set for a mutually beneficial partnership. Am I right!?','I just saw that robot fly into the Forest! Or maybe he went into the town?']
	}
}, {
	id: '10780',
	name: 'Vogon',
	level: 2,
	sprite: 36,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['Vogon knows you have the strength to find this robot and get our color back. Vogon sees all the things. Vogon knows all things. Vogon wants to help you. But first, Vogon wants you to prove yourself. Ready?', 'Vogon is disappointed in you.', 'Why don\'t you talk to Oriole or PenPen? Vogon is done with you.']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'Power and Privilege: Classism',
		feedbackRight: 'Way to take action',
		feedbackWrong: '',
		question: 'Which of the bulleted recomendations, if any, will you commit to?',
		questionType: 'open',
		requiredLength: 50,
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l90,0l0,-60l-50,0l-20,20l-20,40z',
			fill: 'green'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '17959',
	name: 'Quinto',
	level: 3,
	sprite: 37,
	isHolding: false,
	dialog: {
		smalltalk: ['1','I see you\'ve come! The time is here to reflect on what you\'ve done..','You still have a long way to go. Come back later and I will teach the ways of social SCIENCE!']
	}
}, {
	id: '17525',
	name: 'Archibald',
	level: 3,
	sprite: 38,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['Do you ever wonder what the world will be like when you\'re gone? I think the best we can hope for is to leave the world a better place! Hopefuly this bit will help you. Ready?', 'Focus! Try again!', 'Was that resource helpful? I\'m worried about my legacy!']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'Sustainability',
		feedbackRight: 'Right on!',
		feedbackWrong: 'Not quite. Remember, "An Ounce of Prevetion" and all that.',
		question: 'When should you begin to think about the sustailabity of your work?',
		questionType: 'multiple',
		possibleAnswers: ['A) When your work commitment is over','B) During the last few weeks of your commitment','C) During the first few weeks of your commitment','D) Before you even begin'],
		answer: 'D) Before you even begin',
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l-120,0l0,40l240,0c0,0 0,-40 0,-40c0,0 -120,0 -120,0z',
			fill: 'orange'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '12708',
	name: 'Esther',
	level: 3,
	sprite: 39,
	isHolding: false,
	dialog: {
		smalltalk: ['1','Everyone always asks why I wear my coat in warm weather. I have to tell them it\'s my fur and I can\'t take it off! No one understands me...','You can view the puzzle you\'re trying to solve at any time by clicking the toolbox to launch your inventory... but you knew that.']
	}
}, {
	id: '13696',
	name: 'Brumble',
	level: 3,
	sprite: 40,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['I love the water! When you bring all the color back, my water view will be incredible! I want to help. Here\'s a question.', '2', 'Water... pools... reflection pools... reflection... it all makes sense now!']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'Understanding Reflection',
		feedbackRight: 'Great! Now go find my friend Goober to talk more about how you\'ll reflect on things.',
		feedbackWrong: '',
		question: 'In your own words, what is reflection, and why is it important?',
		questionType: 'open',
		requiredLength: 25,
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l0,-40l240,0l0,40l-240,0z',
			fill: 'blue'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '15668',
	name: 'Mageline',
	level: 3,
	sprite: 41,
	isHolding: false,
	dialog: {
		smalltalk: ['1','I wonder who could have built that robot? You know, the Botanist builds things sometimes. He made those special seeds!','I wonder who could have built that robot?']
	}
}, {
	id: '12249',
	name: 'Banksi',
	level: 3,
	sprite: 42,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['What was that? You\'ll have to speak into my good ear. If I hear a right answer from you, I\'ll give you something that will help!', '2', 'I hear you\'ve been reflecting on things. That\'s awesome!']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'Tips For the Future',
		feedbackRight: 'That\'s important to think about.',
		feedbackWrong: '',
		question: 'Which one of these tips do you think most applies to you?',
		questionType: 'open',
		requiredLength: 30,
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l80,0l0,-90l-100,0l20,90z',
			fill: 'lightOrange'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '13246',
	name: 'Grebulon',
	level: 3,
	sprite: 43,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['Are you hear to take my order? Finally! I\'ll have three large black coffees. Oh, it\'s you! I have something for you that might help...', 'I\'ll give you a hint if you give me some COFFEE! Eh, just try again.', 'I know you\'re doing a good job, because most of the color has come back!']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'Leading the Way',
		feedbackRight: 'That\'s something I can get behind.',
		feedbackWrong: '',
		question: 'Are you interested in developing your capacity to be a leader? Why or why not?',
		questionType: 'open',
		requiredLength: 30,
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l-60,0l-40,-180l100,0l-60,60l40,0l20,50l0,70z',
			fill: 'lightGreen'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '14380',
	name: 'Prefect',
	level: 3,
	sprite: 44,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['Hm. You\'re the one who\'s bringing back all the color? I thought you\'d be taller... Oh well. I\'ll still help you.', '2', 'I\'ll give you the same advice I give everyone: Get educated, and watch out for robots!']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'Connected Learning',
		feedbackRight: 'Awesome! I want to take a class on towels, and their relevance to galactic travel.',
		feedbackWrong: '',
		question: 'Complete this thought: I am now interested in taking a course on...',
		questionType: 'open',
		requiredLength: 5,
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l-100,0l0,90l80,0l20,-90z',
			fill: 'green'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '15656',
	name: 'Ford',
	level: 3,
	sprite: 45,
	isHolding: false,
	dialog: {
		smalltalk: ['1','I saw the robot a little while ago. It had this funny look... like it\'s planning something BIG.','Do you make your answers public? You know you can get way moe seeds that way!']
	}
}, {
	id: '16929',
	name: 'Tali',
	level: 3,
	sprite: 46,
	isHolding: false,
	dialog: {
		smalltalk: ['1','The Botanist is great and everything, but he\'s been acting kind of nervous ever since that robot showed up!','You\'re new here! We\'ll help you out later, but first you need to solve more of the enigma!']
	}
}, {
	id: '16920',
	name: 'Boomer',
	level: 3,
	sprite: 47,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['Have you ever thought about where the future might take you? Wherever you go, this resource might help!', '2', 'You\'re like some color prodigy! I feel smarter and more artistic just by knowing you.']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'Future Connections',
		feedbackRight: 'That sounds great. I know you can do it!',
		feedbackWrong: '',
		question: 'Name one connection that you would like to further explore.',
		questionType: 'open',
		requiredLength: 15,
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l-20,-90l160,0l-20,90l-120,0z',
			fill: 'lightGreen'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '15638',
	name: 'Goober',
	level: 3,
	sprite: 48,
	isHolding: true,
	dependsOn: [13696],
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['I thought these things were Raisinets, but they\'re really seeds! Want some? Then answer my question.', '2', 'It\'s peanutbutter jelly time!']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'How You Will Reflect',
		feedbackRight: 'That\'s really great. Thank you!',
		feedbackWrong: '',
		question: 'Select one of the actions on the previous page that you will commit to, and explain your choice.',
		questionType: 'open',
		requiredLength: 20,
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l100,0l-40,180l-60,0l0,-70l20,-50l40,0l-60,-60z',
			fill: 'blue'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '16912',
	name: 'Crumb',
	level: 3,
	sprite: 49,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['I may be little, but I\'m packing some mighty big thoughts. Let\'s see if we\'re on the same wavelength. If we are, I\'ll give you something that just might help you out!', '2', 'Remember, size matters not! Only knowledge. Reflect on that.']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'Where Will You Go From Here?',
		feedbackRight: 'I like it!',
		feedbackWrong: '',
		question: 'Do you see a connection between your work in the community and thoughts about your future career? If so, how?',
		questionType: 'open',
		requiredLength: 10,
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l60,60l-40,0l-20,-20l-20,20l-40,0l60,-60z',
			fill: 'lightOrange'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '15626',
	name: 'Derp',
	level: 3,
	sprite: 50,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['I\'ve still got plenty of seeds left. I\'m supposed to give them to whoever can answer this. Is that you?', 'I can still give you a seed or two if you try again!', 'I\'m raising my hand because I have a question... and you already answered it.']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'The Power of Civic Engagement',
		feedbackRight: 'Yup! Amazing, huh?',
		feedbackWrong: 'Did we read the same resource? Try again.',
		question: 'True or False: According to Dr. Astin\'s study, simply participating in service, with no weight given to the quality results of that service, has a positive impact on a variety of measures, including leadership.',
		questionType: 'truefalse',
		answer: 'true',
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l120,0l0,220l-60,0l-40,-180l-20,0l0,-40z',
			fill: 'orange'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '13360',
	name: 'Overcoat',
	level: 3,
	sprite: 51,
	isHolding: true,
	dialog: {
		prompts: ['I know someone who looks like me, except their coat is really just fur. Can you believe that? Here\'s something else interesting: a question for you to answer.', 'I\'ll give you another shot, but only because I like you.', 'I think we all learned something important, today. When you figure out what it is, tell me! Or better yet, tell the Botanist!']
	},
	resource: {
		tagline: 'What You Leave Behind...',
		feedbackRight: 'Perfect',
		feedbackWrong: 'Close, but think bigger!',
		question: 'Who benefits from evaluating the impact of your work?',
		questionType: 'multiple',
		possibleAnswers: ['A) You','B) The organization(s) running the program','C) The host community where the program was run','D) All of these','E) B and C'],
		answer: 'D) All of these',
		shape: {
			path: 'm0,0l20,20l-20,50l-20,-50l20,-20z',
			fill: 'green'
		}
	}
}, {
	id: '10797',
	name: 'Smalls',
	level: 3,
	sprite: 52,
	isHolding: false,
	dialog: {
		smalltalk: ['1','I\'ve been thinking a lot about the future lately. What will happen if the color just goes away again? What will we do then?','Thanks for bringing the color back, but I worry about the future.']
	}
}];